[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the guy B-Rabbits mother is dating in the movie 8 Mile?", "correct_answer": "Greg Bhuel", "incorrect_answers": ["DJ Iz", "Future", "Cheddar Bob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On average, how many tornadoes are reported in the United States annually?", "correct_answer": "800-1,000", "incorrect_answers": ["2,000-2,500", "3,500-4,000", "3,000-3,200"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Brandon DiCamillo, the stuntman from Jackass: The Movie, specialize in?", "correct_answer": "Doing impressions", "incorrect_answers": ["Running naked", "Getting hurt", "Jumping in elephant poo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these represents the locus of points, the sum of whose distances from two given points is equal?", "correct_answer": "An ellipse", "incorrect_answers": ["A parabola", "A circle", "A hyperbola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the second Republican US President?", "correct_answer": "Ulysses Grant", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Johnson", "Abraham Lincoln", "Rutherford B. Hayes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Wicked Witch of the West from The Wizard of Oz write in the sky, while flying over the Emerald City?", "correct_answer": "Surrender Dorothy", "incorrect_answers": ["Surrender Dorothy or die", "You will die Dorothy", "Surrender or else"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Arthropods were the largest animals on Earth during the Silurian period (443ma-417ma).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous pilot made the first solo flight from Hawaii to the mainland of the USA.", "correct_answer": "Amelia Earhart", "incorrect_answers": ["Howard Hughes", "Tex  Johnston", "Charles Lindbergh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid die at the end of the self-titled movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous fictional character Forrest Gump wins the Congressional Medal of Honor by saving most of the men in his squad. Forrest himself is wounded during his heroic rescue. Where is Forrest wounded?", "correct_answer": "in the buttocks", "incorrect_answers": ["in the stomach", "in the arm", "in the leg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the hotel where Johnny and Penny do a performance each year in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Shelldrake", "incorrect_answers": ["Shalloft", "Catskill", "Bucaroon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This multi-talented family has churned out several projects over the years, most notably the movie Im Gonna Git You Sucka.", "correct_answer": "The Wayans", "incorrect_answers": ["The Jacksons", "The Smiths", "The Winans"]}]